{
    "id": "6883192afbbf4f62a4ec0d3ea82bce7d",
    "title": "Do vs. Does vs. Did",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Whom ………………………. you want to meet?",
            "description": "Use do with you. As there is no reference to past time, use the simple present here.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c513f414e8c04fa2805b36e29da5b7fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………… you do then?",
            "description": "Then shows distance in time. Hence, use the past tense here. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "803b981622ab446aa56ba51e39f8b44d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam ……………………… not have a good job.",
            "description": "Use does with a singular subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb0b2d41b8ec43429d83ad6db036eea1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Leena ……………………….. not want to quit her job.",
            "description": "Did is also possible here however, since there is no reference to past time, use the simple present. ",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b0a3f77cce143fc97e49ebb27f65ff7"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………………….. you know him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17abbd1d2fba421c905c60471f63cf97"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………. they react when they heard the news?",
            "description": "Here the subordinate clause is in the past tense hence, we use a past tense here as well. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1cf21d110fda4e5db908408568e99095"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. you understand the consequences of your action?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "050320af335042b7a771753467c461d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking …………………………. cause cancer.",
            "description": "Use does with singular subjects. Does smoke means the same as smokes. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ff174cedd9d446ba2a9d589d3fee628"
        },
        {
            "question": "That ………………………… not seem plausible.",
            "description": "That is a singular subject hence, we use does with it. Did is also possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f8de97ba082477bb9d33f6cbdfd8113"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you meet him yesterday?",
            "description": "Yesterday is a past time adverb hence, we use did here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87bcf8d66b8141c1a6d4546d8ad44e54"
        },
        {
            "question": "At first she ………………………….. not recognize him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "274340fc3ff94c01abfa5bd00b442206"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents ………………………… not support my desire to become an actor.",
            "description": "Either do not or did not is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54a0ea1625364986bdac32ef9fedfe96"
        }
    ]
}